Guide to the Penn State Extension records 01131
Eberly Family Special Collections Library
- 05: 4-H, 4
  - What They Say About 4-H - A Survey of 4-H Teen Members, undated; cuid1694; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow - A Legacy of Success, undated (Box 283)
  - Your 4-H Swine Program, undated; cuid1695; 1 Items (Box 178)
- 06: Oral Histories, 5
  - Art Ifft, part 1 and Bill Davis, part 2 and Harry Wilcock (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Bucher, part 1 (E. Tait interviewer), July 31, 1976 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Carl Dossin (E. Tait interviewer), March 7, 1979 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Elton Tait, February 20, 1978 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Harry Poorbaugh (E. Tait interviewer), July 15, 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Harry Poorbaugh (E. Tait interviewer), March 7, 1979 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - H. R. "Skip" Kies (E. Tait interviewer), March 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - James F. Keim (E. Tait interviewer), October 19, 1978 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Lyle A. Carter (E. Tait interviewer), 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Margaret Haines (statement on extension) (E. Tait interviewer), March 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Rasmussen (E. Tait interviewer), July 31, 1976 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Stanley Hummer (E. Tait interviewer), September 9, 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 1)
  - Harry S. Sloat - Lancaster Agent, 1921-1961 - statement following outline (E. Tait interviewer), March 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - **************Heritage We Share: Tape clips, Master (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - ************Historical tape done by W. Irvin Galt, Russell M. Smith and William R. Wallace - At time of 50th Anniversary Meeting of Forest County Agricultural Extension Association (E. Tait interviewer), October 29, 1969 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - Harold Waha (E. Tait interviewer), August 26, 1978 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - Eliza Corbin (E. Tait interviewer), March 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - Isabel B. Smith (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - McDougall "MAC" (E. Tait interviewer), August 28, 1976 (E. Tait interviewer) (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - ************Extension Pioneers speak out, master tape clips (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - Betty Patton (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - Chauncey Lang (E. Tait interviewer), July 15, 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - E. J. Parry (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 2)
  - Tom Patton (E. Tait interviewer), 1979 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - E. P. Fowler (E. Tait interviewer), February 5, 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - W. W. Simonds Extension Director (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - ************Fowler (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - E. G. Hamill (E. Tait interviewer), September 9, 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - John Pepper (E. Tait interviewer), March 8, 1979 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - Edinger (E. Tait interviewer), undated (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - Marguerite Erickson Ide (E. Tait Interviewer), January 3, 1977 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - N. C. Dale (E. Tait interviewer), August 27, 1976 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - Poorbaugh (E. Tait interviewer), August 25, 1978 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - J. E. McKeehent (E. Tait interviewer), August 25, 1978 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - Alvin Hacker (E. Tait interviewer), December 31, 1976 (Box 282, Cassette Folder 3)
  - Heritage We Share, 1969; cuid1700; 1 Items; Audio--Cassette--Standard
  - Marquerite Erickson Ide (Interview), Jan. 3, 1977; cuid2618; 2 CD's
  - Violence in Cont. Amer. Society, Conference (2), 1967/05/26; cuid1702; 2 Items; Audio--Tape--
- 07: Photographs and Negatives, 6
  - Charts and Graphs, undated; cuid1703; 5 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Come to Pennsylvania in '85, undated; cuid1704; Photographic--Slides (Box 181)
  - Crops and Vegetation, undated; cuid1705; 6 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Experiments with Crops/Vegetation, undated; cuid1706; 3 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Experiments with Crops/Vegetation - measurements, undated; cuid1707; 2 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Extension photograph album pages, circa 1920-1978 (Box 281)
  - Extension Photos, undated; cuid1708; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Lab Work, undated; cuid1709; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Landscapes, undated; cuid1710; 3 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Men at Work, undated; cuid1711; 4 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Observations on Crops, undated; cuid1712; 1 Items; Photographic--Prints--Black-and-White (Box 181)
  - Adams County - Berks County, 1940-1960 (Box 202)
  - Blair County - Butler County, 1940-1960 (Box 203)
  - Cambria County - Columbia County, 1940-1960 (Box 204)
  - Centre County, 1917-1947 (Box 205)
  - Centre County, 1948-1952 (Box 206)
  - Centre County, 1952-1957 (Box 207)
  - Centre County, 1958-1961 (Box 208)
  - Centre County, 1961 (Box 209)
  - Centre County, Penn State Campus - State College, 1936-1963 (Box 210)
  - Centre County - State College, 1958-1968 (Box 211)
  - Crawford County - Dauphin County, 1940-1960 (Box 212)
  - Delaware County - Huntingdon County, 1940-1960 (Box 213)
  - Indiana County - Lancaster County, 1940-1960 (Box 214)
  - Lawrence County - Mifflin County, 1940-1960 (Box 215)
  - Monroe County - Potter County, 1940-1960 (Box 216)
  - Schuylkill County - Warren County, 1940-1960 (Box 217)
  - Agriculture/Agronomy, 1940-1960 (Box 218)
  - Washington County - York County, 1940-1960 (Box 219)
  - Home Economics, 1940-1960 (Box 220)
  - Agriculture/Horticulture/Ornamental Horticulture - Poultry, 1940-1960 (Box 221)
  - Agriculture Department/Agriculture/Agronomy - Penn State Campus Scenes, 1940-1960 (Box 222)
  - Portrait negatives, undated (Box 200)
- 08: Progress Reports, Circulars, 7
  - Pennsylvania Agriculture Extension Service Special Circulars 1-82, 1949-1960; cuid1713; 1 Items; Textual--Bound Volumes (Box 170)
  - Progress Reports 25-61, 1950-1951; cuid1715; 1 Items; Textual--Bound Volumes (Box 170)
  - Progress Reports 62-107, 1951-1953; cuid1716; 1 Items; Textual--Bound Volumes (Box 170)
  - Progress Reports 108-151, 1953-1956; cuid1714; 1 Items; Textual--Bound Volumes (Box 170)
  - Other
    - Ag Extension Studies #1-87, undated; cuid1717; 1 Items; Microforms--Microfiche
    - Bear Meadows newspaper clippings, 1964-1965; cuid1718; 1 Items (Box 200)
    - Extension Studies, Reels 01-02, 1980/10/23; cuid1719; 2 Items; Microforms--Microfilm--16mm
- 09: EMIS
  - Data sent to Washington Copies of Reports and Printouts, 1971-1977; cuid1720; 1 Items (Box 138)
  - Files, undated; cuid1721; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - Historical Material, undated; cuid1722; 1 Items (Box 140)
  - Narrative Report, 1970-1971; cuid1723; 1 Items (Box 108)
  - Narrative Reports by Project, 1973; cuid1724; 1 Items (Box 115)
  - Newsletters, undated; cuid1725; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - Procedural Information, 1983; cuid1726; 1 Items (Box 157)
  - Reports, 1983; cuid1727; 1 Items (Box 158)
  - Reports, 1983; cuid1728; 1 Items (Box 159)
  - Reports, undated; cuid1729; 1 Items (Box 140)
  - Reports, undated; cuid1730; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - Reports and Printouts, 1974; cuid1731; 1 Items (Box 148)
  - Reports and Printouts, 1976; cuid1732; 1 Items (Box 148)
  - Statistical Reports and Printouts, 1967; cuid1733; 1 Items (Box 150)
- 10: Records
  - 96th Congress 1st Edition, undated; cuid1734; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - AA Maps/Census Data, 1992; cuid1735; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Accomplishment Report, 1988; cuid1736; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Accomplishments and Results Annual Report, 2001-2002 (Box 280)
  - Accomplishments and Results Annual Report, 2002-2003 (Box 277)
  - Accomplishments and Results Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 280)
  - Accomplishments and Results Annual Report, 2006 (Box 278)
  - Activities Summary, 1922-1968; cuid1737; 1 Items (Box 153)
  - Administrative Files and Correspondence, undated; cuid1738; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Administrative Handbook Volume 2, undated; cuid1739; 2 Items (Box 166)
  - Adopt-A-Tree Album, undated; cuid1740; 1 Items (Box 177)
    4-H Forestry Guide
  - Ag Arena - A Project of the Penn State Fund Council, undated; cuid1741; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Ag Extension Publications - Turfgrass and Soil, undated; cuid1742; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Ag Progress Days, 1990/08; cuid1743; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Ag Publications Concerning Pests of Field Crops, undated; cuid1744; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Agribusiness Workshops for Personnel Managers and Supervisors, undated; cuid1745; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agrichemical Fact Sheets - College of Agriculture, undated; cuid1746; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Agricultural Accidents and Rescue Program, undated; cuid1747; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Advisory Council - Symposium on Protection of the Environment and Food Base, undated; cuid1748; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Advisory Council to the Pennsylvania State University College of Agriculture, undated; cuid1749; 2 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Arena Complex - Phase III, undated; cuid1750; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Education at Penn State, undated; cuid1751; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Engineering - An Undergraduate Major Offered Jointly by the College of Agriculture and the College of Engineering at Penn State, undated; cuid1752; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Engineering Fact Sheet, undated; cuid1753; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station - Accomplishments and Results Annual Report, 2002-2006 (Box 279)
  - Agricultural Extension, 1910-1930; cuid1754; 1 Items; Scrapbooks (Box 161)
  - Agricultural Mechanization - A College of Agriculture Major in the Agricultural Engineering Dept. at Penn State, undated; cuid1755; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agricultural Structures - Short Course for Builders, Planners, and Environment Suppliers, 1966/02; cuid1756; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agriculture and Home Economics Extension Service, undated; cuid1757; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Agriculture Chemical Worker's Pest Control School, 1967/08; cuid1758; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agriculture College Harassment and Staff Development Booklets, 2008; cuid2449 (Box 240)
  - Agriculture Extension, undated; cuid1759; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Slide Shows (Box 162)
  - Agriculture Extension Service Annual Report, undated; cuid1760; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Agriculture Extension Work - Brief History, undated; cuid1761; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Agriculture Historical Timetable Calendar, 1962; cuid1762; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - Agriculture: Where the Action Is - Open House, 1967/05; cuid1763; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agronomy, undated; cuid1764; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Agronomy Fact Sheets #12, undated; cuid1765; 1 Items (Box 179)
  - Agronomy with Emphasis on Soil Erosion and Contour Farming, 1936-1939; cuid1766; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Agronomy with Emphasis on Soil Erosion and Contour Farming, 1936-1939; cuid1767; 1 Items; Photographic--Slides--Glass Lantern
  - Alabama Agriculture and Forestry Leadership Development Programs - Alabama LEADERS Program, undated; cuid1768; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Alfalfa Improvement Conference and Forage Insect Research Conference, 1966/07; cuid1769; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Alfalfa Symposium, 1975/04; cuid1770; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - All Region Conference, 2004-2006; cuid2430 (Box 237)
  - All SE Region Conference, 1999-2002; cuid2427 (Box 237)
  - All Staff Conference SE Region, 1998-2001; cuid2426 (Box 237)
  - Alternative Funding Study Group Report, 1999 (Box 279)
  - Alternatives to On-Farm Land Application of Manure, undated; cuid1771; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - American Association of Housing Educators Annual Conference - Housing and Public Policy: The 1980s, 1980/10; cuid1772; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - American Cottage Cheese Institute Annual Meeting, 1965/11; cuid1773; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - American Family Scene Series - The One-Parent Family, undated; cuid1774; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - An Educational Program for Planning and Developing Community Health Services, undated; cuid1775; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - An Insect Management Program for Alfalfa Guide, undated; cuid1776; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - An Introductory Income Tax Workshop for Farmers Preparing their Own Returns, Beginning Tax Preparers, and Others Desiring to Improve their Tax Service, 1979; cuid1777; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Animal Behavior Society - Northeastern Regional Meeting, 1974/11; cuid1778; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Animal Breeding Conference, 1968/12; cuid1779; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Animal By-Products Conference, 1967/06; cuid1780; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Animal Diagnostic Laboratory - Test Directory and Fee Schedule, 1990/01; cuid1781; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Animal Nutrition and Health Seminar, 1968/05; cuid1782; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Anniversary Booklets, undated; cuid1783; 1 Items (Box 148)
  - Anniversary Programs, undated; cuid1784; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Anniversary Programs, 50th, 1962-1969; cuid1785; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - Announcing: the 1966 Agronomy Dealer Workshops (Lime, Fertilizer, Seed, Farm Chemicals), cuid1786; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Annual Action Plans, 1996-1998 (Box 280)
  - Annual Action Plans, 1999 (Box 278)
  - Annual Meeting Minutes, 1924-1969; cuid1787 (Box 190)
  - Annual Meeting of the American Society of Agricultural Engineers in North Atlantic Region, 1966/08; cuid1788; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Annual Meeting of the Pennsylvania Approved Dairy Laboratory Directors Association, 1974-1975/04; cuid1789; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Annual Penn State Square Dance Festival, 1974; cuid1790 (Box 178)
  - Annual Penn State Square Dance Festival, 1978/08; cuid1791; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Annual Progress Reports, 1992; cuid1792; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Annual Progress Reports and Action Plans, 1999; cuid1793; 1 Items (Box 174)
  - Annual Progress Reports and Action Plans, 1995-1998; cuid1794; 4 Items (Box 175)
  - Annual Regional Short Courses in Meat Science and Technology, 1983/06; cuid1795; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Annual Report, 1992 (Box 280)
  - Annual Report, 1994; cuid1796; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Annual Report, 1997; cuid1797; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Annual Report, 1989-1992; cuid1798; 4 Items (Box 176)
  - Annual Report and Annual Update, 1993 (Box 280)
  - Annual Report and Annual Update, 1993-1996; cuid1799; 2 Items (Box 176)
  - Annual Report and Annual Update, 1996-1997 (Box 278)
  - Annual Reports, undated; cuid1800; 1 Items (Box 108)
  - Annual Reports, undated; cuid1801; 1 Items (Box 143)
  - Annual Reports, undated; cuid1802; 1 Items (Box 148)
  - Annual Reports - Printed, undated; cuid1803; 1 Items (Box 116)
  - Annual Reports - Printed, undated; cuid1804; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Annual Reports from other States, undated; cuid1805; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Annual Update, 1989; cuid1806; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Annual Update, 1993; cuid1807; 1 Items (Box 176)
  - Annual Update, 1993 (Box 280)
  - Annual Work Plans, 1992-1993; cuid1808; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Annual Work Plans, 1992-1994 (Box 279)
  - Annual Work Plans, 1993-1995; cuid1809; 3 Items (Box 175)
  - Annual Work Plans, 1995 (Box 280)
  - Applications of Sensory Evaluation in Food Product Development, 1988; cuid1810; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Aquatic Plant Herbicides, 1980; cuid1811; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Are You a Woman in Agriculture?, undated; cuid1812; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Are You Tired All the Time?, undated; cuid1813; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag Guide
  - Are You Watching Your Figure?, undated; cuid1814; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Area Agents, 1980-1981; cuid1815; 1 Items (Box 104)
  - Articles, undated; cuid1816; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - At This Time of Harvest and With Heartfelt Thanks, undated; cuid1817; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Avoid Drug Residues in Goat Meat and Milk, undated; cuid1818; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Babysitting is a Caring Job, undated; cuid1819; 1 Items (Box 177)
    4-H Guide
  - Bag of Tricks for EFNEP Youth Program, undated; cuid1820; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Ag Series
  - Bear Meadows Bog - School of Forest Resources, undated; cuid1821; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Bedding Plants: A Guide to Programmed Disease Control, undated; cuid1822; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Beef Cattle Conference, 1976/03; cuid1823; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Better Trees for Metropolitan Landscapes - A Symposium for Arborists and Tree Breeders, 1975/11; cuid1824; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Beware of Machine Hazards - U.S. Dept. of Labor, 1976; cuid1825; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Bicycle Safety Checklist, undated; cuid1826; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Bone Up on Calcium, undated; cuid1827; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Booklets, undated; cuid1828; 1 Items (Box 145)
  - Books, undated; cuid1829; 1 Items (Box 125)
  - Brochures, Booklets and Newsletters, undated; cuid1830; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Business Management Clinic (Nurserymen, Landscapers, and Landscape Maintenance), 1970/01; cuid1831; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Calf and Heifer Growth Chart, undated; cuid1832; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Camp Program and Maintenance Workshop, 1975/04; cuid1833; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Can Green Beans the Safe Way, undated; cuid1834; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Capitol Complex Listing - Senators and House of Representatives, 1983-1984; cuid1835; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Carbohydrates, Proteins, and Fats, undated; cuid1836; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Card Deck, undated; cuid1837; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - Care and Repair of Electric Cords, undated; cuid1838; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Caregivers Express, undated; cuid1839; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - CED Committee Report, 1986; cuid1840; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - CED File, 1988; cuid1841; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - CED Issues Committee, 1985-2007 (Box 279)
  - CED Leadership Institute, 2007-2008; cuid2433 (Box 237)
  - CED Meetings, 2006-2007; cuid2445 (Box 239)
  - CED Minutes, 2003-2006; cuid2441 (Box 239)
  - Centennial Information Kit, undated; cuid1842; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - Central Extension, 1935-1943; cuid1843; 1 Items; Scrapbooks (Box 160)
  - Central Extension, 1943-1947; cuid1844; 1 Items; Scrapbooks (Box 160)
  - Central Extension Annual Reports of Projects I-V, 1962-1969; cuid1845; 1 Items (Box 124)
  - Central Extension Reports, undated; cuid1846; 1 Items (Box 108)
  - Central Extension Specialist Reports, undated; cuid1847; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - Central Extension Typescript Reports, undated; cuid1848; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - Changing Scene, The, 1956; cuid1849; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
  - Changing Structure of Agriculture Production, undated; cuid1850; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Checklist for a Nursing Home, undated; cuid1851; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Chocolate Manufacture Short Course, 1988/05; cuid1852; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Choosing Recipes, undated; cuid1853; 1 Items (Box 178)
    Foods and Nutrition Extension Guide
  - Citizens Shaping Health Services - Why Extension Should Get Involved and How Extension Can Help, undated; cuid1854; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Citizens' Viewpoint publication, 1990-1992; cuid1855; 1 Items (Box 175)
  - Citizens Working Together on Community Problems - Pennsylvania Title V Rural Development Program, undated; cuid1856; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Citizenship in Action, undated; cuid1857; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Civil Rights and Equal Employment Opportunity, 1989 (Box 277)
  - Civil Rights Annual Reports, 1993-1997 (Box 280)
  - Cleaner Water for Pennsylvania and the Chesapeake Bay, undated; cuid1858; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Clippings, undated; cuid1859; 1 Items (Box 142)
  - Clippings, undated; cuid1860; 1 Items (Box 143)
  - Clippings, undated; cuid1861; 1 Items (Box 145)
  - Clippings, undated; cuid1862; 1 Items (Box 155)
  - College of Ag Letter Concerning Study Materials on Pesticides and Pest Management, undated; cuid1863; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - College of Ag. Posters Describing Health Cleaning Habits, undated; cuid1864; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - College of Agriculture Extension Series, undated; cuid1865; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - College of Agriculture Extension Service, undated; cuid1866; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - College of Agriculture Reception for New Faculty and Staff, 1976/10; cuid1867; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Commercial Christmas Tree Growers Short Course, 1960/05; cuid1868; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Commercial Strawberry Production Guide, undated; cuid1869; 1 Items (Box 177)
  - Common Disease of Turfgrass, undated; cuid1870; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Community Bridge Project Yearly Summary Report, 2002-2003 (Box 278)
  - Computer on the Farm - Educational Service in Farm Management Using Linear Programming, undated; cuid1871; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Conference Materials, undated; cuid1872; 1 Items (Box 117)
  - Conference Materials, undated; cuid1873; 1 Items (Box 121)
  - Conference on Advances in Poultry and Egg Processing, 1968/10; cuid1874; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Conference on Water Conservation and Sewage Flow Reduction with Water-Saving Devices, 1975/04; cuid1875; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Conference Proceedings, undated; cuid1876; 1 Items (Box 109)
  - Conference Proceedings, undated; cuid1877; 1 Items (Box 110)
  - Conferences, Institutes, Workshops, and Seminars, 1968; cuid1878; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Continuing American Revolution: Some Shifting Frontiers in Community Development, 1968/12; cuid1879; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Control of Metabolism, 1970/08; cuid1880; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Control of Metabolism - A Dedicatory Symposium, undated; cuid1881; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Control of Summer Annual Grass Weeds, undated; cuid1882; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Cooking Utensils Guide, undated; cuid1883; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Cooperative Extension Administrative Structure, 1997 (Box 278)
  - Cooperative Extension in Southeast Region: Leadership Team Materials, 2007; cuid2443 (Box 239)
  - Cooperative Ext. Service, undated; cuid1884; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Cooperative Extension News from Penn State, Elton Tate Reporting, 1960-1969; cuid1885; 1 Items; Moving Image--Film--16mm--Positive
  - Cooperative Extension Service, 1987; cuid1886; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Cooperative Extension Service, undated; cuid1887; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Cooperative Extension Service - Early History of, undated; cuid1888; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Cooperative Extension Service - Its Mission in Pennsylvania, undated; cuid1889; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)
  - Cooperative Extension Service and Its Mission in Pennsylvania, undated; cuid1890; 1 Items (Box 166)
  - Cooperative Extension Service Funding, undated; cuid1891; 1 Items (Box 178)
  - Cooperative Extension Service Information, undated; cuid1892 (Box 191)
  - Cooperative Extension: A Pennsylvania Tradition, undated; cuid1893; 1 Items; Textual--Pamphlets (Box 179)